curiositylounge.com 2015-09-19

# Privacy Policy

Effective Apr 1, 2015

**This Policy may change from time to time. Please check back frequently for updates.**

Adknowledge EN, Inc., a Delaware corporation, and Quizrocket.com (“Quizrocket”, “we”, or “us”) respect and protect the privacy of consumers.  This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes what information we collect through Quizrocket.com, how we use that information, and some of your privacy rights regarding that information.

Collection of Information and Your Privacy Rights

What information we collect and how we collect it.

1.1 Collection of Information. Quizrocket collects information from you when you voluntarily provide it to Quizrocket or one of its partners, through websites (owned and operated by Quizrocket or a third party), social networking applications, blogs, and other means (together, these sources are referenced hereafter as "Publishers") (for example, by signing up for an email newsletter or through a co-registration offer on a survey), or by other means of online or offline surveys, order forms, or registration pages operated by third parties (collectively, a "User Form"). In a User Form, Quizrocket or a third party may offer you incentives in exchange for providing information about yourself such as name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers, birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, employment information, and personal and online interests (together, "User Information"). Completing the User Form is voluntary and you are under no obligation to provide User Information.  Information about business partners of Quizrocket, including Publishers and advertisers, may be collected through various means in the course of conducting business operations, such as through agreements entered into by the party and by emails exchanged with those partners (all such information being “Business Information”).

1.2 Vendor List Information. Quizrocket may obtain information about you after you provide information to a third party and you permit that party (the "Seller") to share the information, which Quizrocket subsequently purchases, licenses, or otherwise lawfully acquires. Such information may include, but is not limited to, your name, street address, zip code, telephone numbers, birth date, gender, salary range, education, marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and other information which you provided to the Seller (together, "Vendor List Information"). When acquiring Vendor List Information, Quizrocket requires assurances from the Seller that the Seller has a right to transfer the Vendor List Information to Quizrocket and that Quizrocket may lawfully use the Vendor List Information to transmit offers from advertisers.

1.3 User Behaviors Collected with Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Information. Quizrocket uses cookie and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about you, such as your Internet Protocol address and what Web browser you are using, with certain of your online behaviors, such as opening or clicking on a particular online advertisement. Additionally, Quizrocket may use other new and evolving sources of information and information gathering in the future as they become available (together, "Technology Information").

(a) Cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data stored on the hard drive of your computer that allows Quizrocket and/or its partners to identify and associate your IP address with corresponding information in Quizrocket's database. Quizrocket and/or its third party partners may use cookies to track individual responses or views of advertisements and activity across different websites over time, and use this information to help predict what other advertisements may be of interest to you and enable you to receive customized advertisements or content. These cookies contain no personally identifiable information. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, such as your email address, that we may share with any third party in hashed, non-human readable form. To learn about how you can opt-out of the receipt of cookies, please visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices. To learn about how you can remove cookies placed on your computer or prevent the placement of cookies on your computer, please see Section 4 below. To learn more about cookies in general, please visit http://www.cookiecentral.com.

(b) Web beacons. A web beacon is programming code used to display an image on a web page and can also transfer an individual's user identification to a database and associate the individual with previously acquired information about the individual. Web beacons enable Quizrocket and its third party partners to track certain Web sites you visit or advertisements you view online across different websites over time. Web beacons help determine products or services in which you may be interested and help track online behaviors for marketing purposes. More information about web beacons is available at http://www.webopedia.com/TERM/W/Web_beacon.html.

(c) Where Technology Information is Collected. Technology Information is collected directly from Quizrocket advertisements or indirectly through Publishers that Quizrocket contracts with to display advertisements. Such advertisements will usually be displayed within one of the following advertising vehicles:

Websites. Quizrocket may set a cookie on your computer when you view advertisements delivered on Publisher websites. After a cookie is set, Quizrocket may track how you interact with the advertisement and the Publisher website (for example, registering, purchasing, browsing, etc.).

Software Programs. Similar to Websites, Quizrocket displays banner advertisements in software programs that you may use.

Email Databases. Quizrocket and/or its partners may track your interaction with email advertisements sent to you (for example, by setting a cookie on your computer) on behalf of Publishers, advertisers or partner websites (for example, when you register, purchase, or browse in response to such email).

1.4 Outside Information. Quizrocket may lawfully receive information about you from third parties, such as information located in public databases ("Outside Information").

1.5 No Information Collected from Minors. MINORS UNDER THE AGE OF 13 SHOULD NOT PROVIDE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION, INCLUDING THEIR EMAIL ADDRESS, TO Quizrocket. If Quizrocket is notified it has personal information about a minor under the age of 13, that information will be promptly deleted from our database.

1.6 Individual Information. As used herein, Individual Information means User Information, Vendor List Information, Technology Information, Outside Information, and any other information Quizrocket lawfully obtains about you.

Use of Information and User Data

How we use and share the information we collect.2.1 Discretion to Use Information. Information voluntarily provided to Quizrocket or lawfully obtained by Quizrocket is the property of Quizrocket and may be used by Quizrocket for any lawful purpose, including the sale, lease or transfer of the information to Publishers, advertisers and data aggregators, for marketing purposes. If you wish to end your email subscription with us or one of our Publishers, you may follow the instructions at the end of each email message to unsubscribe or follow the instructions detailed at Section 4 below.

2.2 Targeted Advertising and Information. Quizrocket may use Individual Information to target advertising and other information, such as business, weather, entertainment, sports and general news alerts and similar information, more effectively. When an individual is online, Quizrocket may use Technology Information to associate an individual with their Individual Information and Quizrocket attempts to show information and advertising for products and services to which the person may respond. Quizrocket may use data collected from a response to one type of advertising or information for targeting advertisements or other information through a different venue. For example, Quizrocket may notice that you responded to a baseball banner advertisement and use that response to deliver a baseball-related advertisement and other information to you.

2.3 Legal Process. Quizrocket may disclose Individual Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders and other legal process as required by law.

2.4 Summary Data. Quizrocket may sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons.How we store and protect the information we receive.2.5 Storage of Individual Information. Quizrocket stores Individual Information in a database on Quizrocket computers; the information is maintained and stored in encrypted form. In addition, Quizrocket's computers have security measures, such as a firewall, to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under Quizrocket's control. Quizrocket also maintains physical and procedural safeguards to protect Individual Information. Notwithstanding such measures, Quizrocket cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent these computers from being illegally accessed and the Individual Information on them stolen or altered.

Privacy Practices of Third Parties

3.1 Advertiser cookies and web beacons. Publishers who place advertisements on the Internet may use their own cookies, web beacons and other technology to collect information about you. Quizrocket does not control Publishers' use of such technology. Quizrocket may place cookies of its Publishers or advertisers who are under contract with Quizrocket, on your computer. These cookies may be placed at the time you open and/or click within email sent by Quizrocket or a Publisher under contract with Quizrocket. This Policy does not apply to the practices of Publishers or other companies that Quizrocket does not own or control or to people that Quizrocket does not employ or manage.

3.2 Links. The Publishers' Website and email messages transmitted by Quizrocket on its own behalf or on behalf of Publishers may contain hypertext links to the Websites of third parties. Quizrocket is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other Websites.

3.3 Affiliated Companies that are not Publishers. Quizrocket may disclose or transfer Individual Information to affiliated companies, parent companies, or subsidiaries in Quizrocket's discretion.

How You May Exercise Your Rights

4.1 Websites. To prevent the display of Publisher or Quizrocket advertising on a Website, for example, banner advertisements, do not visit the Website. To only prevent Quizrocket from tracking your behavior on a Website, turn off cookies from that Website and do not click on or interact with any advertisements.  Please note that Quizrocket does not have a mechanism or process to respond to any “do not track” signals which a web browser may send or receive.

4.2 Email Databases. To unsubscribe from Quizrocket or Publisher email lists, click the link included in the footer of any message delivered by Quizrocket or a Publisher and follow the instructions provided. You may also unsubscribe from emails you signed up for at this Website by visiting http://www.Quizrocket.com/unsubscribe.

4.3 Software Programs. To prevent software programs from displaying advertisements on your computer, uninstall the software program provided by a Quizrocket Publisher by following the instructions included in the privacy policy at the time of installation. Software programs should include an option to uninstall in the "Add/Remove Programs" section of the Windows® operating system, or by visiting the file director of the installed program and running an uninstaller executable.

4.4 Cookies. Check instructions about your web browser to learn how to prevent placement of, or how to remove, cookies placed on your computer by Quizrocket.

More Information

5.1 For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit http://www.netcoalition.com and http://www.privacyalliance.org. If you wish to be notified of any updates to this Privacy Policy, please check back frequently as any updates will be posted to Quizrocket with a new effective date. If you have questions about this Policy and your rights under this policy, would like access to personal information we may have about you in our files, to correct, update, or to have us delete it, or would like to notify us of your choice to opt out of the sharing of any of your personal information, please write to us at the address below.  Please note that, notwithstanding any requests otherwise, Business Information may be retained by us as necessary for business or legal purposes.

Quizrocket.com

Attn: Privacy

4600 Madison Ave., 10th Floor

Kansas City, MO 64112
